Guide to the Tim Stevens Papers, 1945-2006 AIS.2006.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- NAACP, 1971-2006; 1994-2004; III.
  - Community Involvement, 1990-2004; 3.
    - YWCA Center for Race Relations, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Family Outreach Day, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Hunger Services Network Jazz, 1996-2002 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Economic Development, 1994-2004; 4.
    This subseries contains material relating to the NAACP's interest in issues of economic development from 1994 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Economic Development Committee.
    - Alliance for Progressive Action, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Assistance for Small Businesses, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Bangs, Ralph, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - Benchmarks, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - Benchmarks, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Benchmarks, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Black Professionals, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - Business Development, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Buying Power, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Capital Assets, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Coliseum, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - Commitment, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 57)
    - Committee Report, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 58)
    - County Presidents, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 59)
    - Dowe, Al, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 60)
    - Dowe's on 9th, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 61)
    - Edwards, Eddie, undated (Box 42, Folder 62)
    - Duquesne Light, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 63)
    - Economic Reciprocity, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 64)
    - Financial Empowerment Guide, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 65)
    - General, 1996-2001 (Box 42, Folder 66)
    - Homeownership and Business Initiative, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 67)
    - Living Wage Campaign, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 68)
    - Living Wage Campaign, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 69)
    - Living Wage Campaign, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 70)
    - National Urban League, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 71)
    - Payday Lending, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 72)
    - Plans, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 73)
    - Plans for Progress, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 74)
    - Plans for Progress, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Plans for Progress, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Predatory Lending Forum, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Regional Sales Tax, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Resolution, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Selective Buying, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Social Security, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Coliseum, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Lemington, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Plans for the Progress, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Education, 1995-2004; 5.
    This subseries contains material relating to the NAACP's interest in educational issues, from 1995 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Education Committee.
    - Affirmative Action, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - African American Alumni Council, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Africana Studies, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Back to School Conference, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Brown v. Board of Education, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Budget Presentation, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Carlow College, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Charter School, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - City of Pittsburgh, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Committee Information, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Committee Report, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Community College of Allegheny County, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Education Policy and Leadership Center, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Education Report, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - General, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - General, 1995-1999 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - General, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 26-27)
    - General, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 28-29)
    - General, 1996-2003 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - General, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - General, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - General, undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Good Schools Pennsylvania, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Hightower Scholars, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Ideas, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Information Renaissance, 1998-2002 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Institute for Community Leadership in Education, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Meetings, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Notes, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Partners Continuum, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1998-2003 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Pittsburgh Technical Institute, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - President's Report, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Scholarships, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - School Board, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - School Board Districts, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - School Board Minority/Women/Disadvantaged Business, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - School Governance, undated (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - School Vouchers, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Wilkins Primary, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Youth March, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Jonny Gammage Scholarship, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Issues, April 2002 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools Math Teachers, May 2002 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee, 1971-2005; 6.
    This subseries contains material concerning the NAACP Executive Committee from 1971 to 2005, with the great bulk of the material focusing on Stevens' presidential tenure from 1994 to 2004.
    - Additions, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Board Appointments, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Board Information, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Board Retreat, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Lavera, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - By-laws, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Changes, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Committee Reports, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Executive Director, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Executive Director, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Executive Director, 1997-2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Executive Director, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
    - Executive Director, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Executive Director, 2002-2005 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Executive Director, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Executive Director Applications, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Executive Director Correspondence, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Executive Director Search, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Executive Officers, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Executive Sessions, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Expectations of Committee Members, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Funerals, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - General, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - General, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - General, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - General Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Goals and Expectations, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Kendrick, Louis, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Installation, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Mandatory Training, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Mandatory Training, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Mandatory Training, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Mandatory Training, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Meetings, 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Meetings, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Meetings, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 38-41)
    - Meetings, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Meetings, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Meetings, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 7-9)
    - Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Meetings, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 11-14)
    - Member Qualifications, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Members, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Memos, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17-19)
    - Memos, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Memos, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 21-22)
    - Memos, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Minutes, 1994-1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Nominees, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Notes, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Officer Responsibilities., undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Officers, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Officers' Meeting, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Officers and Personnel Committee, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Porter, Ron, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Resumes, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Retreat, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Retreat, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Rosen's Board Model, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Plan Goal, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Suggestions, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Training Seminar, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Veteran Affairs, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Vision Statement, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Welcome Letter, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Contact Lists, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Meetings, May 2002 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Notes, April-May 2002 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Leadership Seminar, June 1993 (Box 42, Item 14)
  - Finance, 1993-2005; 7.
    This subseries contains material relating to the NAACP's finances from 1993 to 2005. Included in this are partial records of the Finance Committee.
    - Accounting, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - African American Chamber of Commerce Grant, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Audit, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Audit, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Audit, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Balance Sheet, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Budget, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Capital Assets, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Committee Information, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Committee Meetings, 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Donations, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Expenses, 1993-1999 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Expenses, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Federated Investors, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Financial Report, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Freedom Fund, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Freedom Fund, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Fundraising, 1993-2002 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - General, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - General, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - General, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - General, undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Klein Charitable Remainder Unitrust, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - National Financial Report, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation Grant, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation Grant, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation Grant, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation Grant, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation Report, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - POISE Foundation, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - President's Expenses, 1997-2004 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - Profit and Loss, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - Scholarships, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Scholarships, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Scholarships, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - Scholarships, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Treasurer, 1999-2001 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Treasurer's Report, 1996-2001 (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Invoice, March 2002 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Health, 1999-2004; 8.
    This subseries contains material relating to the NAACP's concern with health issues, from 1999 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Health Committee.
    - Allegheny County Health Department, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - Benefit Cuts, undated (Box 42, Folder 57)
    - Black Papers on African-American Health in Allegheny County, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 58)
    - Brochures, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 59)
    - Citizens for Consumer Justice, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 60)
    - Committee Reports, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 61)
    - General, 1999-2004 (Box 42, Folder 62)
    - High Blood Pressure, undated (Box 42, Folder 63)
    - HIV/AIDS, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 64)
    - Memo, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 65)
    - Mental Health, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 66)
    - Prostate Cancer, 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Report, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Acorn "Credit Insurance" Action, undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Letter, April 2002 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Housing, 1995-2003; 9.
    This subseries contains materials relating to the NAACP's interest in housing issues, from 1995 to 2003. Included in this are partial records of the Housing Committee.
    - Aliquippa Terrace Resident Council, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Assessments, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Demolition, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Fair Housing Partnership, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - General, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - General, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - General, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Housing Authority of Pittsburgh, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sanders Cost, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Labor and Industry, 1994-2004; 10.
    This subseries includes material relating to the NAACP's interest in labor disputes and industrial development, from 1994 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Labor and Industry Committee.
    - African American Workers Union, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Bell Atlantic, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Black Contractors, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Black-owned Media, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Black Tradesmen, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Brochures, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Charlton, Milton, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Children and Youth Services, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Committee Information, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Committee Meetings, 1997-2003 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Committee Members, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Complaint Coordinator, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Complaint Status, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Construction, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Construction Industry, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Construction Site Employment, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Construction Site Summit, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Consumer Choices, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Convention Center, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Corporations, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Economic Reciprocity, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Executive Action Plea for Fairness and Equity, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Flaherty, Tom, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Follow-up, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Flyer Diagram, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - General, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 39-40)
    - General, 1994-2003 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - General, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - House of Crossroads, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Justice for Janitors, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Lemington, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - LM Wiring Technologies, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Meadow Lanes Bowling, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Media Initiative, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Meetings, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Minority Contracting, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Minority Employment in the Construction Industry, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Minority/Women/Disadvantaged Business Enterprise, 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 52-55)
    - Minority/Women/Disadvantaged Business Enterprise Advisory Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Pittsburgh Works, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Plan B, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Plan B, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Plan for Fairness and Equity, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - PNC Bank, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Public Accountability, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Redmond, Gina, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, Carey, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Small Business Administration, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - South Africa Trade Mission, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Sports and Exhibition Authority, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Stadium, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Structural Needs, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Transportation Equality Project, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - University of Pittsburgh Medical Center, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Volunteers, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Women-owned Business, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Legal Redress, 1994-2004; 11.
    This subseries contains materials relating to issues that the NAACP pursued through litigation or legal attention, from 1994 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Legal Redress Committee.
    - Abu-Jamal, Mumia, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Allegheny County Bar Association, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Baumhammer and Taylor, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Civil Rights, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Civil Rights Reference Manual, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Committee Information, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Consent Decree, 1994-2002 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Derzack v. County of Allegheny, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Driving While Black, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Eagle Taxi, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Ethical Standards, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Free Getu Coalition, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - General, 1995-2004 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Hate Crimes, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Jackson, Jerry, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Judicial, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Jury Selection, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Justice Department, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - KDKA, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - KKK, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Law, Thelma, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Legal Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Magisterial District Reestablishment, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Magistrates Court, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Manning, Jeffrey, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Performance Audit, City Magistrates Court, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Pre-paid Legal Services, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Racial Epithets, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Racial Profiling, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - State Ethics Act, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Washington's Slaves, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - West, Robert, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Williams, Ronald, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Young, Adrienne, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Membership, 1994-2004; 12
    This subseries contains material relating to NAACP membership, from 1994 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Membership Committee.
    - Applications, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Appointments to Committees, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Campaign, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Campaigners, undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Church Memberships, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Civil Rights Soldiers, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Collington, Carol, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Committee Information, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Committee Report, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Deaths, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Fees, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Focus Group, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Forms, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Forms, Tim, undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - General, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - General, 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General Membership Involvement, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - General Membership Meetings, 1994-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - General Membership Meetings, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - General Membership Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Graham, Chuck, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Implementation Plan Sample, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Life Memberships, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Meetings, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Membership Award, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Membership Campaign, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Mobilizing, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - National Membership, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Ogburn, Coretta, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Open House, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Personnel, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Recruitment, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Stanton, Delores, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Steeler Memberships, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Task Force, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Taylor, Celeste, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Tim's Membership Drive, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Top Membership Solicitors, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Vann, Dell, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Veterans, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Volunteers, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Volunteers, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Membership/Committee Application, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Personal, 1992-2004; 13.
    This subseries contains material relating to Stevens' individual involvement with the NAACP, mainly campaign material and personal notes, from 1992 to 2004.
    - Accomplishment Scrapbooks, 1994-1996 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Campaign, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Campaign, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Campaign, undated (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Congratulations, 1992-2000 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Election, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Election, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Election, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Installation Clippings, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Mail, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Notes, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Notes, 1996-2003 (Box 42, Folder 40-42)
    - Notes, 1996-2003 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - Notes, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
    - Notes, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
    - Presidential Campaign, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Speeches, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Steubenville Banquet, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Affirmative Action Presentation, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Correspondences, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Elections, 1994-2005 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Notes, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Press Moments, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Speeches, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Police Affairs, 1990-2004; 14.
    This subseries contains materials relating to the NAACP's concern with police affairs in Pittsburgh, from 1990 to 2004. Included in this are partial records of the Police Affairs Committee.
    - Abu-Jamal, Mumia, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Abuse, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - ACLU, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Amnesty International, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Baumhammers, Richard, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Bey, Maneia, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Black Police Officers, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Brookins, Cecil, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Brown, Thomasina, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Chairman's Report, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Citizen Police Review Board, 1996-2003 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Citizens for Police Accountability, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Civil Tension Task Force, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Coalition for African-American Justice, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Committee Meeting, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Committee Report, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Community Centered Policing, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Complaints, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Consent Decree, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Cooperstein, Jeffrey, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 33-34)
    - Diallo, Amadou, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Dixon, Charles, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Driving While Black, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Ellerbe, Michael, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Fraternal Order of Police, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Gammage, Jonny, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Gammage, Jonny, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Gammage, Jonny, "Blind Justice", 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - General, 1995-2004 (Box 19, Folder 5-11)
    - Grimmitt, Deron, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Gross, Evan, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Hill District Shootings, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)